Remember this agent
by can do anything
that you can do
on your computer So
obviously I put it
in a public Discord
and I random people
And I was looking
at it the whole
night People were talking
with it People were
having fun with it
People tried to it
And when my were
like falling off almost
I exited the process
and I to
Though I forgot I
built a system to
be resilient So
while I was walking
to the bedroom the
happily booted up again
and talked to everyone
in the world The
next morning woke up
Over 800 messages I
panicked I pulled the
I read every single
message just
to see if the
leaked my private life
Nothing happened But
it could have